[  
   {  
      "id":1,
      "question":"What do you call the space between Kim Kardashian's breasts and butt cheeks?",
      "answer":"Silicon Valley."
   },
   {  
      "id":2,
      "question":"Why does it take 1 million sperm to fertilize one egg?",
      "answer":"Because like all men, they won't stop to ask directions."
   },
   {  
      "id":3,
      "question":"Which sexual position produces the ugliest children?",
      "answer":"Ask your mother."
   },
   {  
      "id":4,
      "question":"Why is sex like math?",
      "answer":"You add a bed, subtract the clothes, divide the legs, and pray there's no multiplying."
   },
   {  
      "id":5,
      "question":"What kind of bees make milk instead of honey?",
      "answer":"Boo-bees"
   },
   {  
      "id":6,
      "question":"How are fat girls and mopeds alike?",
      "answer":"They are fun to ride, but you don’t want your friends to find out."
   },
   {  
      "id":7,
      "question":"Why do married men gain weight and bachelors don’t?",
      "answer":" The bachelors go to the refrigerator, see nothing they want, then go to bed. Married guys go to bed, see nothing they want, then go to the refrigerator."
   },
   {  
      "id":8,
      "question":"What do you get when you cross an elephant and a rhino?",
      "answer":" Ell-if-I-no (Hell if I know).\n"
   },
   {  
      "id":9,
      "question":"What do you call a lawyer who doesn't know the law?",
      "answer":"A judge."
   },
   {  
      "id":10,
      "question":"What is a Mexican 7-course dinner?",
      "answer":"A taco and a six-pack."
   },
   {  
      "id":11,
      "question":"What did the duck say when he bought lipstick?",
      "answer":"Put it on my bill."
   },
   {  
      "id":12,
      "question":"What did the elephant say to the naked man?",
      "answer":"How do you breathe through something so small?"
   },
   {  
      "id":13,
      "question":"How do you count cows?",
      "answer":"With a cowculator."
   },
   {  
      "id":14,
      "question":"Can a kangaroo jump higher than the Empire State Building?",
      "answer":"Of course. The Empire State Building can't jump."
   },
   {  
      "id":15,
      "question":"How did the blonde try to kill the bird?",
      "answer":"She threw it off a cliff."
   },
   {  
      "id":16,
      "question":"Why did the chicken cross the playground?",
      "answer":"To get to the other slide!!"
   },
   {  
      "id":17,
      "question":"What's the difference between a cat and a complex sentence?",
      "answer":"A cat has claws at the end of its paws and a complex sentence has a pause at the end of its clause."
   },
   {  
      "id":18,
      "question":"Why did the turkey cross the road?",
      "answer":"Because he wasn't a chicken."
   },
   {  
      "id":19,
      "question":"What do you call a rabbit that has fleas?",
      "answer":"Bugs bunny."
   },
   {  
      "id":20,
      "question":" How do fish get high? \n",
      "answer":"Seaweed."
   },
   {  
      "id":21,
      "question":" Why do bunnies have soft sex? \n",
      "answer":"They have cotton balls."
   },
   {  
      "id":22,
      "question":"Why did the dinosaur cross the road?",
      "answer":"Chickens didn't exist yet."
   },
   {  
      "id":23,
      "question":"What did the elephant say to the naked man?",
      "answer":" Cute, cute, but can it pick up peanuts?"
   },
   {  
      "id":24,
      "question":"Why is the barn so noisy?",
      "answer":"Because the cows have horns."
   },
   {  
      "id":25,
      "question":"Q: Why can't a blonde dial 911?",
      "answer":"She can't find the eleven."
   },
   {  
      "id":26,
      "question":"What did the blonde say when she saw the Cheerios box?",
      "answer":"Omg, donut seeds!"
   },
   {  
      "id":27,
      "question":"Why did the blonde tip toe near the medicine cabinet?",
      "answer":"Because she didn't want to wake the sleeping pills!!"
   },
   {  
      "id":28,
      "question":"Why couldn't the blonde add 10 + 5 on a calculator?",
      "answer":"She couldn't find the 10 button."
   },
   {  
      "id":29,
      "question":"Why did the blonde put her iPad in a blender?",
      "answer":"Because she wanted to make apple juice."
   },
   {  
      "id":30,
      "question":"Did you hear about the blonde that got excited?",
      "answer":"She finished a jigsaw puzzle in six months, when the box said, "
   },
   {  
      "id":31,
      "question":"How do you confuse a blonde?",
      "answer":"Put her in a circle and tell her to go to the corner."
   },
   {  
      "id":32,
      "question":"How can you tell when a brunette is actually a blonde who dyes her hair?",
      "answer":"When she trips over the cordless phone."
   },
   {  
      "id":33,
      "question":"How did the blonde die drinking milk?",
      "answer":"The cow fell on her."
   },
   {  
      "id":34,
      "question":"What did the blonde say when she found out she was pregnant?",
      "answer":"I wonder if it's mine."
   },
   {  
      "id":35,
      "question":"What do you call a blonde with a brain?",
      "answer":"A golden retriever."
   },
   {  
      "id":36,
      "question":"How do you get a one handed blonde down from a tree?",
      "answer":"Wave at her."
   },
   {  
      "id":37,
      "question":"What did one saggy boob say to the other saggy boob?",
      "answer":"We better get some support before someone thinks we're nuts!"
   },
   {  
      "id":38,
      "question":"Why do women make better soldiers?",
      "answer":"Because they can bleed for a week and not die."
   },
   {  
      "id":39,
      "question":"How did the medical community come up with the term ",
      "answer":" "
   },
   {  
      "id":40,
      "question":"Why does it take 1 million sperm to fertilize one egg?",
      "answer":"Because like all men, they won't stop to ask directions."
   },
   {  
      "id":41,
      "question":"Why do Asians women have small breasts?",
      "answer":"Because their parents only allow A's."
   },
   {  
      "id":42,
      "question":"How do you make a tissue dance?",
      "answer":"Put a little boogie in it."
   },
   {  
      "id":43,
      "question":"Why do Jewish mothers make great parole officers?",
      "answer":"They never let anyone finish a sentence!"
   },
   {  
      "id":44,
      "question":"What's the difference between England and a teabag?",
      "answer":"A teabag could stay in the cup for longer."
   },
   {  
      "id":45,
      "question":"What do you call two Mexicans playing basketball?",
      "answer":"Juan on Juan."
   },
   {  
      "id":46,
      "question":"Why is England the wettest country?",
      "answer":"Because so many kings and queens have been reigning there."
   },
   {  
      "id":47,
      "question":"What’s the best thing about Switzerland?",
      "answer":"I don't know, but the flag is a big plus."
   },
   {  
      "id":48,
      "question":"What do you call a Mexican that lost his car?",
      "answer":"Carlos."
   },
   {  
      "id":49,
      "question":"Why wasn't Jesus born in Australia?",
      "answer":"God couldn't find three wise men and a virgin."
   },
   {  
      "id":50,
      "question":"Why are there no knock knock jokes about America?",
      "answer":"Because freedom rings!"
   },
   {  
      "id":51,
      "question":"What do you call a Filipino contortionist?",
      "answer":"A Manila folder."
   },
   {  
      "id":52,
      "question":"What's the difference between America and yogurt?",
      "answer":"If you leave yogurt alone for 200 years, it develops a culture."
   },
   {  
      "id":53,
      "question":"Why do the French eat snails?",
      "answer":"They don't like fast food."
   },
   {  
      "id":54,
      "question":"What did one German soldier say to the other when the Americans attacked?",
      "answer":"I did Nazi that coming!"
   },
   {  
      "id":55,
      "question":"Which state has the most questions?",
      "answer":"Alaska."
   },
   {  
      "id":56,
      "question":"How did I get to Iraq?",
      "answer":"Iran."
   },
   {  
      "id":57,
      "question":"How do Germans tie their shoes?",
      "answer":"With little knot-sies!"
   },
   {  
      "id":58,
      "question":"If a plane crashed on the Canada/USA border, where would the survivors be buried?",
      "answer":"You don't bury survivors."
   },
   {  
      "id":59,
      "question":"How do you stop a Mexican tank?",
      "answer":"Shoot the people pushing it."
   },
   {  
      "id":60,
      "question":"Why were the Indians here first?",
      "answer":"They had reservations."
   },
   {  
      "id":61,
      "question":"Why is North Korea not as fun as South Korea?",
      "answer":"Because it has no Seoul."
   },
   {  
      "id":62,
      "question":"An Indian cab driver picked up a Japanese man from a hotel. Along the way, they saw a Honda motorcycle overtake the taxicab and the Japanese guy said, ",
      "answer":"Does anyone remember the Swatch, a watch made in Switzerland? Thank god Croatia didn't come up with the idea first. Just imagine if someone were to ask you what time is it? "
   },
   {  
      "id":63,
      "question":"How do astronomers organize a party?",
      "answer":"They planet."
   },
   {  
      "id":64,
      "question":"Why shouldn't you make fun of a paleontologist?",
      "answer":"Because you will get Jurasskicked."
   },
   {  
      "id":65,
      "question":"Why did the chicken cross the möbius strip?",
      "answer":"To get to the same side."
   },
   {  
      "id":66,
      "question":"Why are Helium, Curium, and Barium the medical elements? ",
      "answer":"Because if you can't heal-ium or cure-ium, you bury-um."
   },
   {  
      "id":67,
      "question":"Why do centipedes have 100 legs?",
      "answer":"So they can walk."
   },
   {  
      "id":68,
      "question":"Why can't you trust an atom?",
      "answer":"Because they make up everything."
   },
   {  
      "id":69,
      "question":"Why are atoms Catholic?",
      "answer":"Because they have mass."
   },
   {  
      "id":70,
      "question":"Why do pirates like algebra?",
      "answer":"Annex"
   },
   {  
      "id":71,
      "question":"What did the 30 degree angle say to the 90 degree angle?",
      "answer":"You think you're always right!"
   },
   {  
      "id":72,
      "question":"Which sexual position produces the ugliest children?",
      "answer":"Ask your mother."
   },
   {  
      "id":73,
      "question":"Did you hear about the two bald guys who put their heads together?",
      "answer":"They made an ass out of themselves!"
   },
   {  
      "id":74,
      "question":"Why are blonde jokes so short?",
      "answer":"So brunettes can remember them."
   },
   {  
      "id":75,
      "question":"How do you leave a jackass in suspense?",
      "answer":"Don't know. I'll tell you tomorrow"
   },
   {  
      "id":76,
      "question":"What's the difference between England and a teabag?",
      "answer":"A teabag could stay in the cup for longer."
   },
   {  
      "id":77,
      "question":"What do you call a bench full of white people?",
      "answer":"The MLB."
   },
   {  
      "id":78,
      "question":"Why did the golfer wear two pairs of pants?",
      "answer":"In case he got a hole in one."
   },
   {  
      "id":79,
      "question":"What has eight arms and an IQ of 60?",
      "answer":"Four guys drinking Bud Light and watching a football game!"
   },
   {  
      "id":80,
      "question":"Why did the coach go back to the bank?",
      "answer":"To get his quarterback!"
   },
   {  
      "id":81,
      "question":"Why does Dwayne Wade wear number 3?",
      "answer":"Because that's the amount of minutes he can stay on the court without getting hurt."
   },
   {  
      "id":82,
      "question":"How do you make NY Jets cookies?",
      "answer":"Put them in a bowl and beat them for three hours."
   },
   {  
      "id":83,
      "question":"How do you make NY Jets cookies?",
      "answer":"Put them in a bowl and beat them for three hours."
   },
   {  
      "id":84,
      "question":"Why is a baseball game a good place to go on a hot day?",
      "answer":"Because there are lots of fans."
   },
   {  
      "id":85,
      "question":"Which sport is always in trouble?",
      "answer":"BADminton."
   },
   {  
      "id":86,
      "question":"How did the blonde fisherman die?",
      "answer":"He was run over by the Zamboni."
   },
   {  
      "id":87,
      "question":"What do the Buffalo Sabres and the Titanic have in common?",
      "answer":"They're both at the bottom of the Atlantic."
   },
   {  
      "id":88,
      "question":"What did March say to the madness?",
      "answer":"What's all that bracket?"
   },
   {  
      "id":89,
      "question":"Why did the cookie go to the doctor's office?",
      "answer":"It was feeling crummy."
   },
   {  
      "id":90,
      "question":"How do you know that carrots are good for your eyesight?",
      "answer":"Have you ever seen a rabbit with glasses?"
   },
   {  
      "id":91,
      "question":"Why are there hardly any dental professionals in Arkansas?",
      "answer":"Because it takes 35 patients to make a full set of teeth."
   },
   {  
      "id":92,
      "question":"Why did the cat go to the hospital?",
      "answer":"To have a CAT scan done."
   },
   {  
      "id":93,
      "question":"Why did Santa have to have his balls removed?",
      "answer":"Because he'd carried his sack over his shoulders one too many times."
   },
   {  
      "id":94,
      "question":"What do you call a nurse with dirty knees?",
      "answer":"The head nurse."
   },
   {  
      "id":95,
      "question":"What's black and brown and looks good on a lawyer?",
      "answer":"A Doberman pinscher."
   },
   {  
      "id":96,
      "question":"Why'd the lawyer go to Heaven?",
      "answer":"Hell was full."
   },
   {  
      "id":97,
      "question":"What do you call a lawyer who doesn't know the law?",
      "answer":"A judge."
   },
   {  
      "id":98,
      "question":"What's the difference between a lawyer and God?",
      "answer":"God doesn't think he's a lawyer."
   },
   {  
      "id":99,
      "question":"What do you call a lawyer who has gone bad?",
      "answer":"Senator."
   },
   {  
      "id":100,
      "question":"Why'd the robber take a bath?",
      "answer":"He wanted to make a clean getaway."
   },
   {  
      "id":101,
      "question":"What's it called when a soldier slips into a fox hole?",
      "answer":"Bestiality"
   },
   {  
      "id":102,
      "question":"What happened when the soldier went into an enemy bar?",
      "answer":"He got bombed."
   },
   {  
      "id":103,
      "question":"Why is there a flap on the back of the Navy uniform?",
      "answer":"So the Marine have something to hold on to."
   },
   {  
      "id":104,
      "question":"How do you stop a lawyer from drowning?",
      "answer":"Shoot him before he hits the water."
   },
   {  
      "id":105,
      "question":"Why did Mickey Mouse get shot?",
      "answer":"Because Donald ducked."
   },
   {  
      "id":106,
      "question":"In the Navy, how do they separate the men from the boys?",
      "answer":"With a crowbar."
   },
   {  
      "id":107,
      "question":"How do you sink a Navy submarine?",
      "answer":"Knock on the door."
   },
   {  
      "id":108,
      "question":"How many lawyers does it take to plaster a wall?",
      "answer":"It depends how hard you throw them."
   },
   {  
      "id":109,
      "question":"Which part of the military do babies join?",
      "answer":"The infantry."
   },
   {  
      "id":110,
      "question":"What does ",
      "answer":"Muscles are required; intellegence not expected."
   },
   {  
      "id":111,
      "question":"What do blondes and beer bottles have in common?",
      "answer":"They're both empty from the neck up."
   },
   {  
      "id":112,
      "question":"Why didn't Hitler drink tequila?",
      "answer":"Cause it made him mean."
   },
   {  
      "id":113,
      "question":"What do you call women who hang out with hookers?",
      "answer":"Support hos."
   },
   {  
      "id":114,
      "question":"How can you tell if a guy likes Moosehead?",
      "answer":"By the antler marks on his thighs"
   },
   {  
      "id":115,
      "question":"What comes after 69?",
      "answer":"Mouthwash."
   },
   {  
      "id":116,
      "question":"What's the definition of bravery?",
      "answer":"A man with diarrhea chancing a fart!"
   },
   {  
      "id":117,
      "question":"Why does a woman pierce her belly button?",
      "answer":"So she can hang an air freshner from it."
   },
   {  
      "id":118,
      "question":"What did one butt cheek say to the other?",
      "answer":"Together, we can stop this s**t."
   },
   {  
      "id":119,
      "question":"Why are constipated people so rude?",
      "answer":"They don't give a crap."
   },
   {  
      "id":120,
      "question":"What do you get when you find a dead blonde in a closet?",
      "answer":"The hide-and-seek champion of 1996."
   },
   {  
      "id":121,
      "question":"What is the definition of agony?",
      "answer":"A one-armed man hanging off a cliff with itchy balls."
   },
   {  
      "id":122,
      "question":"How does a redneck tell the difference between a bull and a cow in the dark?",
      "answer":"He sticks his nose in the animal's ass. If there's a place for his tongue, it's a cow."
   },
   {  
      "id":123,
      "question":"How do you make a baby drink?",
      "answer":"Stick it in the blender."
   },
   {  
      "id":124,
      "question":"What should you do if you come across an elephant?",
      "answer":"Apologize and wipe it off."
   },
   {  
      "id":125,
      "question":"What do Eskimos get from sitting on a block of ice?",
      "answer":"Polaroids."
   },
   {  
      "id":126,
      "question":"How do you know when a blonde has a brain fart?",
      "answer":"Her ears flap."
   },
   {  
      "id":127,
      "question":"Why was the condom flying through the air?",
      "answer":"It got pissed off."
   },
   {  
      "id":128,
      "question":"How do you embarrass an archaeologist?",
      "answer":"Give him a used tampon and ask him what period it came from."
   },
   {  
      "id":129,
      "question":"Why did Captain Kirk piss on the roof of the Enterprise?",
      "answer":"To boldly go where no man has gone before."
   },
   {  
      "id":130,
      "question":"I don't eat food that a dog won't touch. That's my guideline. Try to give tofu to a dog. He goes, 'I don't think so. No.' It's a dog. It licks between its legs and sniffs fire hydrants. If he doesn't like something, I go with that opinion. He's drinking out of the toilet. Find out what he thinks.",
      "answer":""
   },
   {  
      "id":131,
      "question":"What do you call someone who doesn't fart in public?",
      "answer":"A private tooter."
   },
   {  
      "id":132,
      "question":"How did Captain Hook die?",
      "answer":"He wiped his bum with the wrong hand."
   },
   {  
      "id":133,
      "question":"What did one of the prositute's knee say to the other?",
      "answer":"Nothing. They have never met."
   },
   {  
      "id":134,
      "question":"What did the banana say to the vibrator?",
      "answer":"What are you shaking about, it's me she's going to eat."
   },
   {  
      "id":135,
      "question":"What do a bungee jump and a hooker have in common?",
      "answer":"They're both cheap, fast, and if the rubber breaks, you're dead."
   },
   {  
      "id":136,
      "question":"What's the difference between a genealogist and a gynecologist?",
      "answer":"The genealogist checks the family tree and the gynecologist checks the family bush."
   },
   {  
      "id":137,
      "question":"What starts with a P, ends with an E, and has a 1,000 letters?",
      "answer":"Post office."
   },
   {  
      "id":138,
      "question":"What did the green grape say to the purple grape?",
      "answer":"Breathe, stupid!"
   },
   {  
      "id":139,
      "question":"What starts with E, ends with E, and has only 1 letter in it?",
      "answer":"Envelope."
   },
   {  
      "id":140,
      "question":"What did the big chimney say to the little chimney?",
      "answer":"You're too young to smoke."
   },
   {  
      "id":141,
      "question":"Why are ghosts bad liars?",
      "answer":"You can see right through them."
   },
   {  
      "id":142,
      "question":"Why do pilgrims pants fall down?",
      "answer":"Because their belts are on their hats."
   },
   {  
      "id":143,
      "question":"What is the difference between a teacher and a train?",
      "answer":"One says, "
   },
   {  
      "id":144,
      "question":"What's the difference between a guitar and a fish?",
      "answer":"You can tune a guitar, but you can't tuna fish."
   },
   {  
      "id":145,
      "question":"What do you call a woman that sets her bills on fire?",
      "answer":"Bernadette"
   },
   {  
      "id":146,
      "question":"What's red and bad for your teeth?",
      "answer":"A brick."
   },
   {  
      "id":147,
      "question":"What does a skeleton order at a restaurant?",
      "answer":"Spare ribs!"
   },
   {  
      "id":148,
      "question":"Why did the skeleton cross the road?",
      "answer":"To get to the body shop."
   },
   {  
      "id":149,
      "question":"What's the importance of capitalization?",
      "answer":"You can either help your Uncle Jack off a horse or help your uncle jack off a horse."
   },
   {  
      "id":150,
      "question":"How do you make holy water?",
      "answer":"Boil the hell out of it."
   },
   {  
      "id":151,
      "question":"What happens once in a minute and twice in a moment but never in a decade?",
      "answer":"The letter "
   },
   {  
      "id":152,
      "question":"Why are there no knock knock jokes about America?",
      "answer":"Because freedom rings!"
   },
   {  
      "id":153,
      "question":"You're trapped in a room with a tiger, a rattlesnake and a lawyer. You have a gun with two bullets. What should you do?",
      "answer":"Shoot the lawyer. Twice."
   },
   {  
      "id":154,
      "question":"What type of sandals do frogs wear?",
      "answer":"Open-toad!"
   },
   {  
      "id":155,
      "question":"Why did the fish blush?",
      "answer":"Because it saw the ocean's bottom."
   },
   {  
      "id":156,
      "question":"Why did President Obama get two terms?",
      "answer":"Because every black man gets a longer sentence"
   },
   {  
      "id":157,
      "question":"Why is England the wettest country?",
      "answer":"Because so many kings and queens have been reigning there."
   },
   {  
      "id":158,
      "question":"How many politicians does it take to change a light bulb?",
      "answer":"Two: one to change it and another one to change it back again."
   },
   {  
      "id":159,
      "question":"What do you call a lawyer who has gone bad?",
      "answer":"Senator."
   },
   {  
      "id":160,
      "question":"What's the difference between 9/11 and a cow?",
      "answer":"You can't milk a cow for over 10 years."
   },
   {  
      "id":161,
      "question":"What is Rodney King's least favorite band?",
      "answer":"The Police."
   },
   {  
      "id":162,
      "question":"Whats the difference between a politician and a snail?",
      "answer":"One is slimy, a pest, and leaves a trail everywhere and the other is a snail"
   },
   {  
      "id":163,
      "question":"What did Gandhi say to the British, after they asked him to move?",
      "answer":"Nah, mastay."
   },
   {  
      "id":164,
      "question":"What do you get when you combine a sex addict with a lesbian?",
      "answer":"Bill and Hillary."
   },
   {  
      "id":165,
      "question":"What is the chance that a Mexican gets across the border?",
      "answer":"Juan in a million."
   },
   {  
      "id":166,
      "question":"What did Saddam Hussein and Little Miss Muffit have in common?",
      "answer":"They both had curds (Kurds) in their way (whey)."
   },
   {  
      "id":167,
      "question":"Why does the queen carry a scepter?",
      "answer":"Because everyone works 'cept her."
   },
   {  
      "id":168,
      "question":"Why do Mexicans eat beans for dinner?",
      "answer":"So they can take bubble baths."
   },
   {  
      "id":169,
      "question":"How come oysters never donate to charity?",
      "answer":"Because they are shellfish."
   },
   {  
      "id":170,
      "question":"Have you ever had Ethiopian food?",
      "answer":"Neither have they."
   },
   {  
      "id":171,
      "question":"What happens when you stick your hand in a jar of jelly beans?",
      "answer":"The black one steals your watch."
   },
   {  
      "id":172,
      "question":"What kind of candy do Indians give out on Halloween?",
      "answer":"Dots."
   },
   {  
      "id":173,
      "question":"Why don't Mexicans like to barbecue?",
      "answer":"Because the beans fall through the grill."
   },
   {  
      "id":174,
      "question":"What does a skeleton order at a restaurant?",
      "answer":"Spare ribs!"
   },
   {  
      "id":175,
      "question":"What kind of key opens a banana?",
      "answer":"A monkey."
   },
   {  
      "id":176,
      "question":"What do a dildo and soy beans have in common?",
      "answer":"They are both used as a meat substitute."
   },
   {  
      "id":177,
      "question":"What did the grape say when it was stepped on?",
      "answer":"Nothing, it just let out a little wine."
   },
   {  
      "id":178,
      "question":"What do you call a cow with two legs?",
      "answer":"Lean beef."
   },
   {  
      "id":179,
      "question":"How do you get a blond on the roof?",
      "answer":"You tell her the food is on the house."
   },
   {  
      "id":180,
      "question":"Why did the tofu cross the road?",
      "answer":"To prove he wasn't chicken."
   },
   {  
      "id":181,
      "question":"What do you get from a pampered cow?",
      "answer":"Spoiled milk."
   },
   {  
      "id":182,
      "question":"What is crazy and walks along the sides of buildings?",
      "answer":"A walnut."
   },
   {  
      "id":183,
      "question":"Why did was the Mexican fast food vendor arrested?",
      "answer":"He was planning a tacover."
   },
   {  
      "id":184,
      "question":"Why can't you tell an egg a joke?",
      "answer":"Because it will crack up."
   },
   {  
      "id":185,
      "question":"What do you call a sad coffee?",
      "answer":"Depresso."
   },
   {  
      "id":186,
      "question":"What's a race car's favorite thing to eat for lunch?",
      "answer":"Fast food!"
   },
   {  
      "id":187,
      "question":"How can you drop a raw egg onto a concrete floor without cracking it?",
      "answer":"Any way you want, concrete floors are very hard to crack."
   },
   {  
      "id":188,
      "question":"How do you turn white chocolate into dark chocolate?",
      "answer":"Turn off the light."
   },
   {  
      "id":189,
      "question":"What was Ludwig van Beethoven's favorite fruit?",
      "answer":"Ba-na-na-na!"
   },
   {  
      "id":190,
      "question":"What is the Mexican version of One Direction?",
      "answer":"Juan Direction."
   },
   {  
      "id":191,
      "question":"What's the difference between Usain Bolt and Hitler?",
      "answer":"Usain Bolt can finish a race."
   },
   {  
      "id":192,
      "question":"What did Obi-Wan say to Luke at the breakfast table?",
      "answer":"Use the fork, Luke."
   },
   {  
      "id":193,
      "question":"What do you call the space between Kim Kardashian's breasts and butt cheeks?",
      "answer":"Silicon Valley."
   },
   {  
      "id":194,
      "question":"A brunette a blonde and a redhead are all in third grade. Who is the oldest?",
      "answer":" The blonde, because she's 18."
   },
   {  
      "id":195,
      "question":"Did you hear about the cat that drank 5 bowls of water?",
      "answer":" He set a new lap record."
   },
   {  
      "id":196,
      "question":"Did you hear about the cat that swallowed a ball of wool?",
      "answer":" She had mittens."
   },
   {  
      "id":197,
      "question":"Did you hear about the man who lost his whole left side?",
      "answer":" He is all-right now."
   },
   {  
      "id":198,
      "question":"Did you hear the joke about the butter?",
      "answer":" Don't worry, you will only spread it."
   },
   {  
      "id":199,
      "question":"Have you heard about the restaurant on the moon?",
      "answer":" It has great food but no atmosphere."
   },
   {  
      "id":200,
      "question":"Have you heard the story about the cat on the tin roof?",
      "answer":" Never mind, it's over your head."
   },
   {  
      "id":201,
      "question":"How can you make a witch itch?",
      "answer":" Take away her â€œWâ€."
   },
   {  
      "id":202,
      "question":"How can you stop a skunk from smelling?",
      "answer":" Hold its nose shut."
   },
   {  
      "id":203,
      "question":"How can you tell a fax has been sent from a blonde?",
      "answer":" There's a stamp on it."
   },
   {  
      "id":204,
      "question":"How can you tell if a guy you're dating is lazy?",
      "answer":" He throws his kisses."
   },
   {  
      "id":205,
      "question":"How can you tell when a blonde rejects a new brain transplant?",
      "answer":" She sneezes."
   },
   {  
      "id":206,
      "question":"How come oysters never donate to charity?",
      "answer":" Because they are shellfish."
   },
   {  
      "id":207,
      "question":"How did a cat take first prize at the bird show?",
      "answer":" He just jumped up to the cage, reached in, and took it."
   },
   {  
      "id":208,
      "question":"How did cows feel when the branding iron was invented?",
      "answer":" They were impressed."
   },
   {  
      "id":209,
      "question":"How did the blonde break her leg raking leaves?",
      "answer":" She fell out of the tree."
   },
   {  
      "id":210,
      "question":"How did the blonde burn her ear?",
      "answer":" The phone rang while she was ironing."
   },
   {  
      "id":211,
      "question":"How did the blonde burn her nose?",
      "answer":" Bobbing for French fries."
   },
   {  
      "id":212,
      "question":"How did the blonde die drinking milk?",
      "answer":" The cow fell on top of her."
   },
   {  
      "id":213,
      "question":"How did the blonde try to kill a bird?",
      "answer":" She threw it off a cliff."
   },
   {  
      "id":214,
      "question":"How did the blonde try to kill a fish?",
      "answer":" By drowning it."
   },
   {  
      "id":215,
      "question":"How did the cat feel after the dog chased it through a screen door?",
      "answer":" Strained."
   },
   {  
      "id":216,
      "question":"How did the farmer fix his jeans?",
      "answer":" With a cabbage patch."
   },
   {  
      "id":217,
      "question":"How did the rainbow know it was lost?",
      "answer":" It was a clear day."
   },
   {  
      "id":218,
      "question":"How did the woman feel when she got run over by a car?",
      "answer":" Tired."
   },
   {  
      "id":219,
      "question":"How do a blonde's brain cells die?",
      "answer":" Alone."
   },
   {  
      "id":220,
      "question":"How do cats buy things?",
      "answer":" From a cat-alogue!"
   },
   {  
      "id":221,
      "question":"How do cats end a fight?",
      "answer":" They hiss and make up."
   },
   {  
      "id":222,
      "question":"How do you amuse a blonde for hours?",
      "answer":" Give her a sheet of paper with Please turn over written on both sides."
   },
   {  
      "id":223,
      "question":"How do you confuse a blonde?",
      "answer":" You don't. They're born that way."
   },
   {  
      "id":224,
      "question":"How do you fix a broken tomato?",
      "answer":" With tomato paste."
   },
   {  
      "id":225,
      "question":"How do you get a blonde out of a tree?",
      "answer":" Wave at her."
   },
   {  
      "id":226,
      "question":"How do you get a blonde to climb on the roof?",
      "answer":" Tell her that the drinks are on the house."
   },
   {  
      "id":227,
      "question":"How do you get a blonde to stay in the shower all day?",
      "answer":" Give her the bottle of shampoo that says, Lather, rinse, repeat."
   },
   {  
      "id":228,
      "question":"How do you get a guitar player to play softer?",
      "answer":" Give him some sheet music."
   },
   {  
      "id":229,
      "question":"How do you get milk from a cat?",
      "answer":" Steal her saucer."
   },
   {  
      "id":230,
      "question":"How do you hire an elephant?",
      "answer":" Stand it on 4 bricks."
   },
   {  
      "id":231,
      "question":"How do you keep a dog from barking in your front yard?",
      "answer":" Put him in your back yard."
   },
   {  
      "id":232,
      "question":"How do you keep someone in suspense?",
      "answer":" Oh, I'll tell you tomorrow."
   },
   {  
      "id":233,
      "question":"How do you know a blonde has been in your office?",
      "answer":" There is white-out on your computer screen."
   },
   {  
      "id":234,
      "question":"How do you know if you cat's got a bad cold?",
      "answer":" He has cat-arrh!"
   },
   {  
      "id":235,
      "question":"How do you know if your cat has eaten a duckling ?",
      "answer":" She's got that down-in-the mouth look!"
   },
   {  
      "id":236,
      "question":"How do you know when a blonde has been making chocolate chip cookies?",
      "answer":" You find M&M shells all over the kitchen floor."
   },
   {  
      "id":237,
      "question":"How do you know when the cat is in the Army?",
      "answer":" When he wears stripes."
   },
   {  
      "id":238,
      "question":"How do you make a bandstand?",
      "answer":" Take their chairs away."
   },
   {  
      "id":239,
      "question":"How do you make a blonde laugh on Saturday?",
      "answer":" Tell her a joke on Wednesday."
   },
   {  
      "id":240,
      "question":"How do you make a blonde's eyes twinkle?",
      "answer":" Shine a flashlight in her ear."
   },
   {  
      "id":241,
      "question":"How do you make an apple turnover?",
      "answer":" Push it downhill."
   },
   {  
      "id":242,
      "question":"How do you make antifreeze?",
      "answer":" You steal her blanket."
   },
   {  
      "id":243,
      "question":"How do you make gold soup?",
      "answer":" Put 14 carrots in it."
   },
   {  
      "id":244,
      "question":"How do you make milk shake?",
      "answer":" Give it a good scare."
   },
   {  
      "id":245,
      "question":"How do you measure a blonde's intelligence?",
      "answer":" Stick a tire pressure gauge in her ear."
   },
   {  
      "id":246,
      "question":"How do you prevent a summer cold?",
      "answer":" Catch it in the winter."
   },
   {  
      "id":247,
      "question":"How do you recognize a blonde at a car wash?",
      "answer":" She's the one on her bike."
   },
   {  
      "id":248,
      "question":"How do you start an insect race?",
      "answer":" One, two, fleaâ€¦Go!"
   },
   {  
      "id":249,
      "question":"How do you stop a charging rhinoceros?",
      "answer":" Take away his credit cards."
   },
   {  
      "id":250,
      "question":"How does a blonde kill a worm?",
      "answer":" She buries it."
   },
   {  
      "id":251,
      "question":"How does a blonde spell farm?",
      "answer":" E-I-E-I-O."
   },
   {  
      "id":252,
      "question":"How does a cat sing scales?",
      "answer":" Do-ri-me-ow!"
   },
   {  
      "id":253,
      "question":"How does a ghost start a letter?",
      "answer":" Tomb it may concern."
   },
   {  
      "id":254,
      "question":"How does a group of dolphins make a decision?",
      "answer":" Flipper coin."
   },
   {  
      "id":255,
      "question":"How does the cat get its own way?",
      "answer":" With friendly purrsuasion."
   },
   {  
      "id":256,
      "question":"How is cat food sold?",
      "answer":" Usually purr-can."
   },
   {  
      "id":257,
      "question":"How many cats can you put into an empty box?",
      "answer":" Only one. After that, the box isn't empty."
   },
   {  
      "id":258,
      "question":"How many months have 28 days?",
      "answer":" All of them."
   },
   {  
      "id":259,
      "question":"How much does it cost a pirate to get their ears pierced?",
      "answer":" A Buc-an-ear."
   },
   {  
      "id":260,
      "question":"If a cat can jump five feet high then why can't it jump through a three foot window?",
      "answer":" Because the window is closed."
   },
   {  
      "id":261,
      "question":"If an apple a day keeps the doctor away what does an onion do?",
      "answer":" Keeps everyone away."
   },
   {  
      "id":262,
      "question":"If lights run on electricity and cars run on gas what do cats run on?",
      "answer":" Their paws."
   },
   {  
      "id":263,
      "question":"If there are ten cats on a boat and one jumps off how many cats are left on the boat?",
      "answer":" None! They were copy cats."
   },
   {  
      "id":264,
      "question":"If two's company and three a crowd what's four and five?",
      "answer":" Nine."
   },
   {  
      "id":265,
      "question":"On a turkey which side would you find most feathers?",
      "answer":" The outside."
   },
   {  
      "id":266,
      "question":"There are 17 blondes standing outside a bar but why can't they get in?",
      "answer":" The sign says â€œMust be 18 to enter.â€"
   },
   {  
      "id":267,
      "question":"To whom do fish go to borrow money?",
      "answer":" The loan shark."
   },
   {  
      "id":268,
      "question":"Two flies are on the porch. Which one is the actor?",
      "answer":" The one on the screen."
   },
   {  
      "id":269,
      "question":"Two silk worms were in a race. What was the result?",
      "answer":" A tie."
   },
   {  
      "id":270,
      "question":"What animal needs oil?",
      "answer":" The mouse, because it squeaks."
   },
   {  
      "id":271,
      "question":"What animals are on legal documents?",
      "answer":" Seals."
   },
   {  
      "id":272,
      "question":"What are the two hardest years in a blonde's life?",
      "answer":" Sixth grade."
   },
   {  
      "id":273,
      "question":"What bird is always out of breath?",
      "answer":" A puffin."
   },
   {  
      "id":274,
      "question":"What bird steals from the rich to give to the poor?",
      "answer":" Robin Hood."
   },
   {  
      "id":275,
      "question":"What birds spend all their time on their knees?",
      "answer":" Birds of prey."
   },
   {  
      "id":276,
      "question":"What can strike a blonde without her ever knowing about it?",
      "answer":" A thought."
   },
   {  
      "id":277,
      "question":"What dance do hippies hate?",
      "answer":" A square dance."
   },
   {  
      "id":278,
      "question":"What did Cinderella say when her photos weren't ready?",
      "answer":" Some day my prints will come."
   },
   {  
      "id":279,
      "question":"What did one angel say to the other angel?",
      "answer":" Halo."
   },
   {  
      "id":280,
      "question":"What did one campfire say to the other?",
      "answer":" Shall we go out one of these nights?"
   },
   {  
      "id":281,
      "question":"What did one eye say to the other?",
      "answer":" Between you and me, something smells."
   },
   {  
      "id":282,
      "question":"What did one math book say to the other?",
      "answer":" Man, I got a lot of problems."
   },
   {  
      "id":283,
      "question":"What did one mountain say to the other mountain?",
      "answer":" Let's meet in the valley."
   },
   {  
      "id":284,
      "question":"What did one plate say to the other plate?",
      "answer":" Lunch is on me."
   },
   {  
      "id":285,
      "question":"What did one tube of glue say to the other tube of glue?",
      "answer":" We have to stick together."
   },
   {  
      "id":286,
      "question":"What did the adding machine say to the cashier?",
      "answer":" You can count on me."
   },
   {  
      "id":287,
      "question":"What did the beach say as the tide came in?",
      "answer":" Long time, no sea."
   },
   {  
      "id":288,
      "question":"What did the bee say to the flower?",
      "answer":" Hi honey."
   },
   {  
      "id":289,
      "question":"What did the big chimney say to the little chimney?",
      "answer":" You're too young to smoke."
   },
   {  
      "id":290,
      "question":"What did the blonde bring to the Super Bowl?",
      "answer":" A spoon."
   },
   {  
      "id":291,
      "question":"What did the blonde do when she missed the 66 Bus?",
      "answer":" She took the 33 bus twice instead."
   },
   {  
      "id":292,
      "question":"What did the blonde name her pet Zebra?",
      "answer":" Spot."
   },
   {  
      "id":293,
      "question":"What did the blonde put under Education on her job application?",
      "answer":" Hooked On Phonics."
   },
   {  
      "id":294,
      "question":"What did the blonde say when she opened the box of Cheerios?",
      "answer":" Oh, look...doughnut seeds!"
   },
   {  
      "id":295,
      "question":"What did the blonde say when she saw the sign in front of the YMCA?",
      "answer":" Look! They spelled MACY'S wrong!"
   },
   {  
      "id":296,
      "question":"What did the burger say when it pleaded â€˜not guilty'?",
      "answer":" I've been flamed!"
   },
   {  
      "id":297,
      "question":"What did the cat say when he lost all his money?",
      "answer":" I'm paw!"
   },
   {  
      "id":298,
      "question":"What did the chewing gum say to the shoe?",
      "answer":" I'm stuck on you."
   },
   {  
      "id":299,
      "question":"What did the chicken say when she got to the library?",
      "answer":" Book, book, book, book, book."
   },
   {  
      "id":300,
      "question":"What did the confused bee say?",
      "answer":" To bee or not to bee."
   },
   {  
      "id":301,
      "question":"What did the digital clock say to his mother?",
      "answer":" Look Mom, no hands!"
   },
   {  
      "id":302,
      "question":"What did the dog say when it sat on sandpaper?",
      "answer":" Ruff!"
   },
   {  
      "id":303,
      "question":"What did the female cat say to the male cat?",
      "answer":" You're the purrfect cat for me!"
   },
   {  
      "id":304,
      "question":"What did the football coach say to the broken vending machine?",
      "answer":" Give me my quarterback!"
   },
   {  
      "id":305,
      "question":"What did the frog say to the chicken in the library?",
      "answer":" Read it, read it, read it, read it."
   },
   {  
      "id":306,
      "question":"What did the letter say to the stamps?",
      "answer":" Stick with me, and we'll go places."
   },
   {  
      "id":307,
      "question":"What did the mayonnaise say when someone opened the refrigerator door?",
      "answer":" Close the door, I am dressing!"
   },
   {  
      "id":308,
      "question":"What did the mermaid say to the man?",
      "answer":" Sea you later."
   },
   {  
      "id":309,
      "question":"What did the mother snake say to her crying baby?",
      "answer":" Stop crying and viper your nose."
   },
   {  
      "id":310,
      "question":"What did the mountain climber name his son?",
      "answer":" Cliff."
   },
   {  
      "id":311,
      "question":"What did the painter say to the wall?",
      "answer":" One more crack, and I'll plaster you."
   },
   {  
      "id":312,
      "question":"What did the picture say to the other picture?",
      "answer":" I heard you got framed."
   },
   {  
      "id":313,
      "question":"What did the picture say to the wall?",
      "answer":" I've got you covered."
   },
   {  
      "id":314,
      "question":"What did the right shoe say to the left shoe?",
      "answer":" I think we must be sole mates."
   },
   {  
      "id":315,
      "question":"What did the silly comedian bake on his day off?",
      "answer":" Cornbread."
   },
   {  
      "id":316,
      "question":"What did the snake say when another asked him the time?",
      "answer":" Don't asp me."
   },
   {  
      "id":317,
      "question":"What did the talking hat say to the scarf?",
      "answer":" You can hang around. I'll just go on ahead."
   },
   {  
      "id":318,
      "question":"What did the termite say when he entered the bar?",
      "answer":" Is the bar tender here?"
   },
   {  
      "id":319,
      "question":"What did the toilet say to the other toilet?",
      "answer":" You look a little flushed."
   },
   {  
      "id":320,
      "question":"What did Zero say to Eight?",
      "answer":" Nice belt!"
   },
   {  
      "id":321,
      "question":"What do a blonde and a beer bottle have in common?",
      "answer":" Both are completely empty from the neck up."
   },
   {  
      "id":322,
      "question":"What do cat actors say on stage ?",
      "answer":" Tabby or not tabby!"
   },
   {  
      "id":323,
      "question":"What do cats like to eat for breakfast?",
      "answer":" Mice Krispies."
   },
   {  
      "id":324,
      "question":"What do cats use to make coffee?",
      "answer":" A purrcolator."
   },
   {  
      "id":325,
      "question":"What do elves do after school?",
      "answer":" Gnomework."
   },
   {  
      "id":326,
      "question":"What do frogs eat with their hamburgers?",
      "answer":" French flies."
   },
   {  
      "id":327,
      "question":"What do golfers use in China?",
      "answer":" China tees."
   },
   {  
      "id":328,
      "question":"What do people in prison use to communicate with one another?",
      "answer":" Cell phones."
   },
   {  
      "id":329,
      "question":"What do pigs put on their sore toes?",
      "answer":" Oinkment."
   },
   {  
      "id":330,
      "question":"What do porcupines say after they kiss?",
      "answer":" Ouch!"
   },
   {  
      "id":331,
      "question":"What do potatoes wear to bed?",
      "answer":" Their yammies."
   },
   {  
      "id":332,
      "question":"What do reindeer say before telling you a joke?",
      "answer":" This one will sleigh you."
   },
   {  
      "id":333,
      "question":"What do sea monsters eat?",
      "answer":" Fish and ships."
   },
   {  
      "id":334,
      "question":"What do skeletons say before a meal?",
      "answer":" Bone appetite."
   },
   {  
      "id":335,
      "question":"What do they serve at birthday parties in Heaven?",
      "answer":" Angel food cake."
   },
   {  
      "id":336,
      "question":"What do vampires have at 11 o'clock every day?",
      "answer":" A coffin break."
   },
   {  
      "id":337,
      "question":"What do you call 10 blondes standing ear to ear?",
      "answer":" A wind tunnel."
   },
   {  
      "id":338,
      "question":"What do you call 4 blondes lying on the ground?",
      "answer":" An air mattress."
   },
   {  
      "id":339,
      "question":"What do you call a baby monkey?",
      "answer":" A chimp off the old block."
   },
   {  
      "id":340,
      "question":"What do you call a blonde behind a steering wheel?",
      "answer":" An airbag."
   },
   {  
      "id":341,
      "question":"What do you call a blonde between two brunettes?",
      "answer":" A mental block."
   },
   {  
      "id":342,
      "question":"What do you call a blonde on a college campus?",
      "answer":" A visitor."
   },
   {  
      "id":343,
      "question":"What do you call a blonde skeleton in the closet?",
      "answer":" Last year's hide and seek champion."
   },
   {  
      "id":344,
      "question":"What do you call a blonde with 90% of her intelligence gone?",
      "answer":" Divorced."
   },
   {  
      "id":345,
      "question":"What do you call a blonde with an IQ of 100?",
      "answer":" Four blondes."
   },
   {  
      "id":346,
      "question":"What do you call a blonde with half a brain?",
      "answer":" Gifted."
   },
   {  
      "id":347,
      "question":"What do you call a boomerang that doesn't work?",
      "answer":" A stick."
   },
   {  
      "id":348,
      "question":"What do you call a brunette between two blondes?",
      "answer":" An interpreter."
   },
   {  
      "id":349,
      "question":"What do you call a cat that has joined the Red Cross?",
      "answer":" A first-aid kit!"
   },
   {  
      "id":350,
      "question":"What do you call a cat that has swallowed a duck?",
      "answer":" A duck filled fatty puss."
   },
   {  
      "id":351,
      "question":"What do you call a cat that lives in an igloo?",
      "answer":" An eskimew."
   },
   {  
      "id":352,
      "question":"What do you call a cat that never comes when she is called?",
      "answer":" Im-puss-able."
   },
   {  
      "id":353,
      "question":"What do you call a cat wearing shoes?",
      "answer":" Puss in boots."
   },
   {  
      "id":354,
      "question":"What do you call a cow in an earthquake?",
      "answer":" A milkshake."
   },
   {  
      "id":355,
      "question":"What do you call a cow that won't give milk?",
      "answer":" A milk dud."
   },
   {  
      "id":356,
      "question":"What do you call a cow with a twitch?",
      "answer":" Beef Jerky."
   },
   {  
      "id":357,
      "question":"What do you call a crazy chicken?",
      "answer":" A cookoo cluck."
   },
   {  
      "id":358,
      "question":"What do you call a deer with no eyes?",
      "answer":" No eye-deer."
   },
   {  
      "id":359,
      "question":"What do you call a dentist in the Army?",
      "answer":" A drill sergeant."
   },
   {  
      "id":360,
      "question":"What do you call a donkey with ear muffs on?",
      "answer":" Anything you want. He can't hear you."
   },
   {  
      "id":361,
      "question":"What do you call a fight between film actors?",
      "answer":" Star Wars."
   },
   {  
      "id":362,
      "question":"What do you call a fish with no eyes?",
      "answer":" A fsh."
   },
   {  
      "id":363,
      "question":"What do you call a fly buzzing inside a blonde's head?",
      "answer":" A Space Invader."
   },
   {  
      "id":364,
      "question":"What do you call a fly that doesn't have any wings?",
      "answer":" A walk."
   },
   {  
      "id":365,
      "question":"What do you call a man who doesn't sink?",
      "answer":" Bob."
   },
   {  
      "id":366,
      "question":"What do you call a man with a car on his head?",
      "answer":" Jack."
   },
   {  
      "id":367,
      "question":"What do you call a rude bird?",
      "answer":" A mockingbird."
   },
   {  
      "id":368,
      "question":"What do you call a scared dinosaur?",
      "answer":" A nervous Rex."
   },
   {  
      "id":369,
      "question":"What do you call a shoe made from a banana?",
      "answer":" A Slipper."
   },
   {  
      "id":370,
      "question":"What do you call a sleeping cow?",
      "answer":" A bulldozer."
   },
   {  
      "id":371,
      "question":"What do you call a smart blonde?",
      "answer":" A golden retriever."
   },
   {  
      "id":372,
      "question":"What do you call a snake that works for the government?",
      "answer":" A civil serpent."
   },
   {  
      "id":373,
      "question":"What do you call a tired cow?",
      "answer":" Milked out."
   },
   {  
      "id":374,
      "question":"What do you call an ant that likes to be alone?",
      "answer":" An independ-ant."
   },
   {  
      "id":375,
      "question":"What do you call an ant with frog legs?",
      "answer":" An antphibian."
   },
   {  
      "id":376,
      "question":"What do you call an easy-going rabbit?",
      "answer":" Hoppy-Go-Lucky."
   },
   {  
      "id":377,
      "question":"What do you call an eternity?",
      "answer":" Four blondes at a 4-way stop."
   },
   {  
      "id":378,
      "question":"What do you call an illegally parked frog?",
      "answer":" Toad."
   },
   {  
      "id":379,
      "question":"What do you call four Spanish cats in quicksand?",
      "answer":" Quatro sinko."
   },
   {  
      "id":380,
      "question":"What do you call it when a blonde dyes her hair brunette?",
      "answer":" Artificial intelligence."
   },
   {  
      "id":381,
      "question":"What do you call it when a cat bites?",
      "answer":" Catnip!"
   },
   {  
      "id":382,
      "question":"What do you call it when a cat stops?",
      "answer":" A paws."
   },
   {  
      "id":383,
      "question":"What do you call newborn kittens that keep getting passed from owner to owner?",
      "answer":" Chain litter."
   },
   {  
      "id":384,
      "question":"What do you call the cat that was caught by the police?",
      "answer":" The purrpatrator."
   },
   {  
      "id":385,
      "question":"What do you call two banana peels on the floor?",
      "answer":" A pair of slippers."
   },
   {  
      "id":386,
      "question":"What do you do when two snails have a fight?",
      "answer":" Leave them to slug it out."
   },
   {  
      "id":387,
      "question":"What do you find at the end of everything?",
      "answer":" The letter g."
   },
   {  
      "id":388,
      "question":"What do you get if you cross a cat with a parrot?",
      "answer":" A carrot!"
   },
   {  
      "id":389,
      "question":"What do you get if you cross an elephant and a fish?",
      "answer":" A swimming trunk."
   },
   {  
      "id":390,
      "question":"What do you get when mixing a tiger and a snowman?",
      "answer":" Frost Bite."
   },
   {  
      "id":391,
      "question":"What do you get when two giraffes collide?",
      "answer":" A giraffic jam."
   },
   {  
      "id":392,
      "question":"What do you get when you cross a cat with a lemon?",
      "answer":" A sourpuss."
   },
   {  
      "id":393,
      "question":"What do you get when you cross a chick with an alley cat?",
      "answer":" A peeping tom."
   },
   {  
      "id":394,
      "question":"What do you get when you cross a parrot with a centipede?",
      "answer":" A walkie-talkie."
   },
   {  
      "id":395,
      "question":"What do you get when you offer a blonde a penny for her thoughts?",
      "answer":" Change."
   },
   {  
      "id":396,
      "question":"What do you give a sick horse?",
      "answer":" Cough stirrup."
   },
   {  
      "id":397,
      "question":"What do you say to the skeleton going on vacation?",
      "answer":" Bone voyage."
   },
   {  
      "id":398,
      "question":"What do you say when you meet a two-headed monster?",
      "answer":" Hello, hello."
   },
   {  
      "id":399,
      "question":"What do you see when you look directly into a blonde's eyes?",
      "answer":" The back of her head."
   },
   {  
      "id":400,
      "question":"What do you use to comb a cat?",
      "answer":" A catacomb."
   },
   {  
      "id":401,
      "question":"What does a baby computer call his father?",
      "answer":" Data."
   },
   {  
      "id":402,
      "question":"What does a bunny use when it goes fishing?",
      "answer":" A harenet."
   },
   {  
      "id":403,
      "question":"What does a cat call a bowl of mice?",
      "answer":" A purrfect meal!"
   },
   {  
      "id":404,
      "question":"What does a cat do when it gets mad?",
      "answer":" It has a hissy fit."
   },
   {  
      "id":405,
      "question":"What does a cat like to eat on a hot day?",
      "answer":" A mice cream cone."
   },
   {  
      "id":406,
      "question":"What does a cat that lives near the beach have in common with Christmas?",
      "answer":" Sandy Claws."
   },
   {  
      "id":407,
      "question":"What does a cell phone give his girlfriend?",
      "answer":" A ring."
   },
   {  
      "id":408,
      "question":"What does a frog say when it washes a car window?",
      "answer":" Rub it, rub it, rub it."
   },
   {  
      "id":409,
      "question":"What does a postcard from a blonde's vacation say?",
      "answer":" Having a fantastic time. Where am I?"
   },
   {  
      "id":410,
      "question":"What does an educated owl say?",
      "answer":" Whom."
   },
   {  
      "id":411,
      "question":"What does an envelope say when you lick it?",
      "answer":" Nothing. It just shuts up."
   },
   {  
      "id":412,
      "question":"What does an octopus wear in the winter?",
      "answer":" A coat of arms."
   },
   {  
      "id":413,
      "question":"What does one star say to another star when they meet?",
      "answer":" Glad to meteor."
   },
   {  
      "id":414,
      "question":"What does the blonde do when someone says it's chilly outside?",
      "answer":" She grabs a bowl."
   },
   {  
      "id":415,
      "question":"What does the blonde make best for dinner?",
      "answer":" Reservations."
   },
   {  
      "id":416,
      "question":"What does the blonde say the last two words of the National Anthem are?",
      "answer":" Play ball!"
   },
   {  
      "id":417,
      "question":"What does the ocean say to the boat?",
      "answer":" Nothing. It just waves."
   },
   {  
      "id":418,
      "question":"What dog loves to take bubble baths?",
      "answer":" A shampoodle."
   },
   {  
      "id":419,
      "question":"What famous painting do cows love to look at?",
      "answer":" The Moona Lisa."
   },
   {  
      "id":420,
      "question":"What followed the dinosaur?",
      "answer":" Its tail."
   },
   {  
      "id":421,
      "question":"What food can make you rich?",
      "answer":" Fortune cookies."
   },
   {  
      "id":422,
      "question":"What game do cows like to play?",
      "answer":" Moonopoly."
   },
   {  
      "id":423,
      "question":"What goes up but never comes down?",
      "answer":" Your age."
   },
   {  
      "id":424,
      "question":"What happened to the blonde who got locked in a grocery store?",
      "answer":" She starved to death."
   },
   {  
      "id":425,
      "question":"What happened to the naughty little witch at school?",
      "answer":" She was ex-spelled."
   },
   {  
      "id":426,
      "question":"What happened when the blonde heard that 90% of all crimes were around the home?",
      "answer":" She moved."
   },
   {  
      "id":427,
      "question":"What happened when the cat went to the flea circus?",
      "answer":" He stole the whole show!"
   },
   {  
      "id":428,
      "question":"What happened when the computer fell on the floor?",
      "answer":" It slipped a disk."
   },
   {  
      "id":429,
      "question":"What happened when the cow tried to jump over a barbed wire fence?",
      "answer":" Udder destruction."
   },
   {  
      "id":430,
      "question":"What happened when the owl lost his voice?",
      "answer":" He didn't give a hoot."
   },
   {  
      "id":431,
      "question":"What happened when the wheel was invented?",
      "answer":" It caused a revolution."
   },
   {  
      "id":432,
      "question":"What happens if you eat yeast and shoe polish?",
      "answer":" Everyday you'll rise and shine."
   },
   {  
      "id":433,
      "question":"What happens if you see twin witches?",
      "answer":" You won't be able to tell which witch is witch."
   },
   {  
      "id":434,
      "question":"What happens to a grape when a man steps on it?",
      "answer":" It lets out a little whine."
   },
   {  
      "id":435,
      "question":"What happens to gold when it's exposed to air?",
      "answer":" Stolen."
   },
   {  
      "id":436,
      "question":"What has forty feet and sings?",
      "answer":" The school choir."
   },
   {  
      "id":437,
      "question":"What has four wheels no wings and flies?",
      "answer":" A garbage truck."
   },
   {  
      "id":438,
      "question":"What has lots of teeth but cannot chew?",
      "answer":" A comb."
   },
   {  
      "id":439,
      "question":"What has more lives than a cat?",
      "answer":" A frog, because it croaks every night."
   },
   {  
      "id":440,
      "question":"What has ten letters and starts with gas?",
      "answer":" An automobile."
   },
   {  
      "id":441,
      "question":"What hired killer never goes to jail?",
      "answer":" The exterminator."
   },
   {  
      "id":442,
      "question":"What insect runs away from everything?",
      "answer":" A flea."
   },
   {  
      "id":443,
      "question":"What is a black cat's favorite TV show?",
      "answer":" Miami Mice!"
   },
   {  
      "id":444,
      "question":"What is a blonde doing when she holds her hands tightly over her ears?",
      "answer":" She's trying to hold onto a thought."
   },
   {  
      "id":445,
      "question":"What is a blonde's favorite part of the gas station?",
      "answer":" The air pump."
   },
   {  
      "id":446,
      "question":"What is a blonde's favorite rock group?",
      "answer":" Air Supply."
   },
   {  
      "id":447,
      "question":"What is a cat's favorite car?",
      "answer":" The Catillac."
   },
   {  
      "id":448,
      "question":"What is a cat's favorite color?",
      "answer":" Purrrrrrrple!"
   },
   {  
      "id":449,
      "question":"What is a cat's favorite movie?",
      "answer":" The Sound of Mewsic."
   },
   {  
      "id":450,
      "question":"What is a cat's favorite snack?",
      "answer":" Mice Cakes!"
   },
   {  
      "id":451,
      "question":"What is a cat's favorite song?",
      "answer":" Three Blind Mice."
   },
   {  
      "id":452,
      "question":"What is a cat's favorite subject in school?",
      "answer":" HISStory."
   },
   {  
      "id":453,
      "question":"What is a cat's way of keeping law & order?",
      "answer":" Claw Enforcement."
   },
   {  
      "id":454,
      "question":"What is a dog's favorite hobby?",
      "answer":" Collecting fleas."
   },
   {  
      "id":455,
      "question":"What is a French cat's favorite pudding ?",
      "answer":" Chocolate mousse!"
   },
   {  
      "id":456,
      "question":"What is a mosquito's favorite sport?",
      "answer":" Skin-diving."
   },
   {  
      "id":457,
      "question":"What is a python's favorite pop group?",
      "answer":" Squeeze."
   },
   {  
      "id":458,
      "question":"What is a slug?",
      "answer":" A snail with a housing problem."
   },
   {  
      "id":459,
      "question":"What is a tree's favorite drink?",
      "answer":" Root beer."
   },
   {  
      "id":460,
      "question":"What is a volcano?",
      "answer":" A mountain with the hiccups."
   },
   {  
      "id":461,
      "question":"What is an elf's favorite cake?",
      "answer":" Shortcake."
   },
   {  
      "id":462,
      "question":"What is black and white and pink all over?",
      "answer":" An embarrassed zebra."
   },
   {  
      "id":463,
      "question":"What is full of holes but can still hold water?",
      "answer":" A sponge."
   },
   {  
      "id":464,
      "question":"What is it that even the most careful person overlooks?",
      "answer":" His nose."
   },
   {  
      "id":465,
      "question":"What is smarter than a spelling bee?",
      "answer":" A talking cat."
   },
   {  
      "id":466,
      "question":"What is taller when it sits down than when it stands up?",
      "answer":" A dog."
   },
   {  
      "id":467,
      "question":"What is Tarzan's favorite Christmas song?",
      "answer":" Jungle Bells."
   },
   {  
      "id":468,
      "question":"What is the best hand to write with?",
      "answer":" Neither; it's best to write with a pen."
   },
   {  
      "id":469,
      "question":"What is the best way to communicate with a fish?",
      "answer":" Drop it a line."
   },
   {  
      "id":470,
      "question":"What is the cannibal's favorite game?",
      "answer":" Swallow the leader."
   },
   {  
      "id":471,
      "question":"What is the cat's favorite TV show?",
      "answer":" The evening mews!"
   },
   {  
      "id":472,
      "question":"What is the cat's favorite magazine?",
      "answer":" Good Mousekeeping."
   },
   {  
      "id":473,
      "question":"What is the definition of gross ignorance?",
      "answer":" 144 blondes."
   },
   {  
      "id":474,
      "question":"What is the difference between a frog and a cat?",
      "answer":" A frog croaks all the time, a cat only nine times."
   },
   {  
      "id":475,
      "question":"What is the difference between a smart blonde and a UFO?",
      "answer":" There have been sightings of UFOs."
   },
   {  
      "id":476,
      "question":"What is the difference between a well-dressed man and a dog?",
      "answer":" The man wears a suit, the dog just pants."
   },
   {  
      "id":477,
      "question":"What is the Easter Bunny's favorite sport?",
      "answer":" Basketball."
   },
   {  
      "id":478,
      "question":"What is the fruitiest lesson?",
      "answer":" History, because it's full of dates."
   },
   {  
      "id":479,
      "question":"What is the most slippery country in the world?",
      "answer":" Greece."
   },
   {  
      "id":480,
      "question":"What is the name of the unauthorized autobiography of the cat?",
      "answer":" Hiss and Tell."
   },
   {  
      "id":481,
      "question":"What is the strongest bird?",
      "answer":" A crane."
   },
   {  
      "id":482,
      "question":"What jam can't be eaten on toast?",
      "answer":" A traffic jam."
   },
   {  
      "id":483,
      "question":"What job function does a blonde have in an M&M factory?",
      "answer":" Proof-reading."
   },
   {  
      "id":484,
      "question":"What kind of animal is always found at baseball games?",
      "answer":" The bat."
   },
   {  
      "id":485,
      "question":"What kind of car does Mickey Mouse's wife drive?",
      "answer":" A minnie van."
   },
   {  
      "id":486,
      "question":"What kind of cat will keep your grass short?",
      "answer":" A Lawn Meower."
   },
   {  
      "id":487,
      "question":"What kind of cats lay around the house?",
      "answer":" Car-pets."
   },
   {  
      "id":488,
      "question":"What kind of cheese isn't yours?",
      "answer":" Nacho Cheese."
   },
   {  
      "id":489,
      "question":"What kind of dog tells time?",
      "answer":" A watch dog."
   },
   {  
      "id":490,
      "question":"What kind of food is crazy about money?",
      "answer":" A dough-nut."
   },
   {  
      "id":491,
      "question":"What kind of hair do oceans have?",
      "answer":" Wavy."
   },
   {  
      "id":492,
      "question":"What kind of horses go out after dark?",
      "answer":" Nightmares."
   },
   {  
      "id":493,
      "question":"What kind of keys do kids like to carry?",
      "answer":" Cookies."
   },
   {  
      "id":494,
      "question":"What kind of music do most mountains like?",
      "answer":" Rock music."
   },
   {  
      "id":495,
      "question":"What kind of physician works on cruise liner?",
      "answer":" A dry doc."
   },
   {  
      "id":496,
      "question":"What kind of rooms have no walls?",
      "answer":" Mushrooms."
   },
   {  
      "id":497,
      "question":"What kind of snacks to do little monkeys have with their milk?",
      "answer":" Chocolate chimp cookies."
   },
   {  
      "id":498,
      "question":"What kind of work does a weak cat do?",
      "answer":" Light mouse work."
   },
   {  
      "id":499,
      "question":"What lies at the bottom of the ocean and twitches?",
      "answer":" A nervous wreck."
   },
   {  
      "id":500,
      "question":"What lights up a soccer stadium?",
      "answer":" A soccer match."
   },
   {  
      "id":501,
      "question":"What looks like half a cat?",
      "answer":" The other half!"
   },
   {  
      "id":502,
      "question":"What mouse was a Roman emperor?",
      "answer":" Julius Cheeser."
   },
   {  
      "id":503,
      "question":"What musical is about a train conductor?",
      "answer":" My Fare, Lady."
   },
   {  
      "id":504,
      "question":"What never gets any wetter no matter how much it rains?",
      "answer":" The sea."
   },
   {  
      "id":505,
      "question":"What people travel the most?",
      "answer":" Romans."
   },
   {  
      "id":506,
      "question":"What pet makes the loudest noise?",
      "answer":" A trum-pet."
   },
   {  
      "id":507,
      "question":"What runs but never walks?",
      "answer":" Water."
   },
   {  
      "id":508,
      "question":"What side of the cat has the most fur?",
      "answer":" The OUT-side."
   },
   {  
      "id":509,
      "question":"What snakes are good at sums?",
      "answer":" Adders."
   },
   {  
      "id":510,
      "question":"What sport do cats play?",
      "answer":" Hairball."
   },
   {  
      "id":511,
      "question":"What stories do the ship captain's children like to hear?",
      "answer":" Ferry tales."
   },
   {  
      "id":512,
      "question":"What three letters alter boys into men and girls into women?",
      "answer":" AGE."
   },
   {  
      "id":513,
      "question":"What time did the man go to the dentist?",
      "answer":" Tooth hurty."
   },
   {  
      "id":514,
      "question":"What time is it when an elephant sits on a fence?",
      "answer":" Time to get a new fence."
   },
   {  
      "id":515,
      "question":"What time is it when seven cats are chasing a mouse?",
      "answer":" Seven after one."
   },
   {  
      "id":516,
      "question":"What type of bow can never be tied?",
      "answer":" A Rainbow."
   },
   {  
      "id":517,
      "question":"What vegetable needs a plumber?",
      "answer":" A leek."
   },
   {  
      "id":518,
      "question":"What works in a circus walks a tightrope and has claws?",
      "answer":" An acrocat! "
   },
   {  
      "id":519,
      "question":"What would you do if a blonde threw a hand grenade right at you?",
      "answer":" You'd pull the pin and throw it back."
   },
   {  
      "id":520,
      "question":"What would you get if you crossed a pig with a karate expert?",
      "answer":" Pork chops."
   },
   {  
      "id":521,
      "question":"What would you get if you crossed an electric eel with a sponge?",
      "answer":" A shock absorber."
   },
   {  
      "id":522,
      "question":"What's the best way to see a charging herd of elephants?",
      "answer":" On TV."
   },
   {  
      "id":523,
      "question":"What's the difference between a tiger and a lion?",
      "answer":" A tiger has the mane part missing."
   },
   {  
      "id":524,
      "question":"What's the unluckiest kind of cat to have?",
      "answer":" A catastrophe!"
   },
   {  
      "id":525,
      "question":"What's 5 miles long and has an IQ of 60?",
      "answer":" A blonde parade."
   },
   {  
      "id":526,
      "question":"What's an insect's favorite sport?",
      "answer":" Cricket."
   },
   {  
      "id":527,
      "question":"What's another name for a helpful Eskimo?",
      "answer":" A Cool Aide."
   },
   {  
      "id":528,
      "question":"What's happening when you hear woof... splat... meow... splat?",
      "answer":" It's raining cats and dogs."
   },
   {  
      "id":529,
      "question":"What's the definition of a will?",
      "answer":" It's a dead giveaway."
   },
   {  
      "id":530,
      "question":"What's the difference between a blonde and a supermarket cart?",
      "answer":" The supermarket cart has a mind of its own."
   },
   {  
      "id":531,
      "question":"What's the richest kind of air?",
      "answer":" Billionaire."
   },
   {  
      "id":532,
      "question":"When a dirty kid has finished taking a bath what is still dirty?",
      "answer":" The bathtub."
   },
   {  
      "id":533,
      "question":"When do vampires bite you?",
      "answer":" On Wincedays."
   },
   {  
      "id":534,
      "question":"When does Friday come before Thursday?",
      "answer":" In the dictionary."
   },
   {  
      "id":535,
      "question":"When is a baseball player like a thief?",
      "answer":" When he steals a base."
   },
   {  
      "id":536,
      "question":"When is a car not a car?",
      "answer":" When it turns into a garage."
   },
   {  
      "id":537,
      "question":"When is a door not a door?",
      "answer":" When it's ajar."
   },
   {  
      "id":538,
      "question":"When is a man like a dog?",
      "answer":" When he is a boxer."
   },
   {  
      "id":539,
      "question":"When is it unlucky to see a black cat?",
      "answer":" When you're a mouse."
   },
   {  
      "id":540,
      "question":"When is the water in the shower musical?",
      "answer":" When it's piping hot."
   },
   {  
      "id":541,
      "question":"Where can you find an ocean with no water?",
      "answer":" On a map."
   },
   {  
      "id":542,
      "question":"Where did the fortune teller go on her vacation?",
      "answer":" Palm Beach."
   },
   {  
      "id":543,
      "question":"Where did the kittens go on their class trip?",
      "answer":" To a mewseum."
   },
   {  
      "id":544,
      "question":"Where do baby ghosts go during the day?",
      "answer":" Dayscare Centers."
   },
   {  
      "id":545,
      "question":"Where do burgers like to dance?",
      "answer":" At a meatball."
   },
   {  
      "id":546,
      "question":"Where do cats write down notes?",
      "answer":" Scratch Paper!"
   },
   {  
      "id":547,
      "question":"Where do cows go on a Saturday night?",
      "answer":" To the Mooooo-vies."
   },
   {  
      "id":548,
      "question":"Where do dogs go when they lose their tails?",
      "answer":" To the retail store."
   },
   {  
      "id":549,
      "question":"Where do kings keep their armies?",
      "answer":" In their sleevies."
   },
   {  
      "id":550,
      "question":"Where do rabbits settle their legal disputes?",
      "answer":" In a pellet court."
   },
   {  
      "id":551,
      "question":"Where do snowmen go to dance?",
      "answer":" A snowball."
   },
   {  
      "id":552,
      "question":"Where do tough chickens come from?",
      "answer":" Hard boiled eggs."
   },
   {  
      "id":553,
      "question":"Where do very smart hot dogs end up?",
      "answer":" On honor rolls."
   },
   {  
      "id":554,
      "question":"Where do you find a dog with no legs?",
      "answer":" Right where you left him."
   },
   {  
      "id":555,
      "question":"Where does a black bird go for a drink?",
      "answer":" To a crow bar."
   },
   {  
      "id":556,
      "question":"Where does success come before work?",
      "answer":" In the dictionary."
   },
   {  
      "id":557,
      "question":"Where is one place that your cat can sit but you can't?",
      "answer":" Your lap."
   },
   {  
      "id":558,
      "question":"Where is the best place to park a dog?",
      "answer":" In a barking lot."
   },
   {  
      "id":559,
      "question":"Which are the strongest creatures in the ocean?",
      "answer":" Mussels."
   },
   {  
      "id":560,
      "question":"Which ballet do pigs like best?",
      "answer":" Swine Lake."
   },
   {  
      "id":561,
      "question":"Which dance do burgers do best?",
      "answer":" The char-char."
   },
   {  
      "id":562,
      "question":"Which game did the cat want to play with the mouse?",
      "answer":" Catch."
   },
   {  
      "id":563,
      "question":"Which is the laziest mountain?",
      "answer":" Ever-rest."
   },
   {  
      "id":564,
      "question":"Which president was least guilty?",
      "answer":" Lincoln. He is in a cent."
   },
   {  
      "id":565,
      "question":"Which word in the dictionary is spelled incorrectly?",
      "answer":" Incorrectly."
   },
   {  
      "id":566,
      "question":"Who always steals the soap in the bathroom?",
      "answer":" The robber ducky."
   },
   {  
      "id":567,
      "question":"Who can shave six times a day and still have a full beard?",
      "answer":" A barber."
   },
   {  
      "id":568,
      "question":"Who does Dracula get letters from?",
      "answer":" His fang club."
   },
   {  
      "id":569,
      "question":"Who granted the fish's wish?",
      "answer":" The Fairy Cod Mother."
   },
   {  
      "id":570,
      "question":"Who helped Cinderella's cat go to the ball?",
      "answer":" Her furry Godmother."
   },
   {  
      "id":571,
      "question":"Who invented King Arthur's round table?",
      "answer":" Sir Cumference."
   },
   {  
      "id":572,
      "question":"Who invented underground tunnels?",
      "answer":" A mole."
   },
   {  
      "id":573,
      "question":"Who went into the witch's den and came out alive?",
      "answer":" The witch."
   },
   {  
      "id":574,
      "question":"Why are astronauts successful people?",
      "answer":" Because they always go up in the world."
   },
   {  
      "id":575,
      "question":"Why are cats better than babies?",
      "answer":" Because you only have to change a litter box once a day."
   },
   {  
      "id":576,
      "question":"Why are cats such good singers?",
      "answer":" Because they're very mewsical."
   },
   {  
      "id":577,
      "question":"Why are elephants so wrinkled?",
      "answer":" They are too hard to iron."
   },
   {  
      "id":578,
      "question":"Why are fish so easy to weigh?",
      "answer":" Because they have their own scales."
   },
   {  
      "id":579,
      "question":"Why are movies stars so cool?",
      "answer":" Because they have so many fans."
   },
   {  
      "id":580,
      "question":"Why are Teddy Bears never hungry?",
      "answer":" Because they are always stuffed."
   },
   {  
      "id":581,
      "question":"Why can't a blonde make Kool-Aid?",
      "answer":" Because she can't fit 8 cups of water in the little packet."
   },
   {  
      "id":582,
      "question":"Why can't a blonde write the number 11?",
      "answer":" She doesn't know which number comes first."
   },
   {  
      "id":583,
      "question":"Why can't a man living in the U.S. be buried in Canada?",
      "answer":" Because he's still alive."
   },
   {  
      "id":584,
      "question":"Why can't a blonde dial 911?",
      "answer":" She can't find the 11 on the phone."
   },
   {  
      "id":585,
      "question":"Why can't a leopard hide?",
      "answer":" Because he's always spotted."
   },
   {  
      "id":586,
      "question":"Why couldn't the blonde manage to make ice cubes?",
      "answer":" She couldn't find the recipe."
   },
   {  
      "id":587,
      "question":"Why couldn't the chicken find her eggs?",
      "answer":" She mislaid them."
   },
   {  
      "id":588,
      "question":"Why couldn't the skeleton go to the dance?",
      "answer":" He had no body to go with."
   },
   {  
      "id":589,
      "question":"Why did a kid throw a clock out the window?",
      "answer":" To see time fly."
   },
   {  
      "id":590,
      "question":"Why did a person with an unspayed female cat have to go to court?",
      "answer":" For kitty littering."
   },
   {  
      "id":591,
      "question":"Why did Bob throw the butter out the window?",
      "answer":" He wanted to see butter fly."
   },
   {  
      "id":592,
      "question":"Why did Mickey Mouse take a trip into space?",
      "answer":" He wanted to find Pluto."
   },
   {  
      "id":593,
      "question":"Why did the blonde buy a brown cow?",
      "answer":" To get chocolate milk."
   },
   {  
      "id":594,
      "question":"Why did the blonde climb the chain-link fence?",
      "answer":" To see what was on the other side."
   },
   {  
      "id":595,
      "question":"Why did the blonde drive into the ditch?",
      "answer":" To turn the blinker off."
   },
   {  
      "id":596,
      "question":"Why did the blonde drown?",
      "answer":" Someone left a scratch & sniff sticker at the bottom of the pool."
   },
   {  
      "id":597,
      "question":"Why did the blonde fall down?",
      "answer":" She tripped over her cordless phone."
   },
   {  
      "id":598,
      "question":"Why did the blonde get fired from the M&M factory?",
      "answer":" For throwing out the W's."
   },
   {  
      "id":599,
      "question":"Why did the blonde have tire tread marks on her back?",
      "answer":" From crawling across the street when the pedestrian sign said DON'T WALK."
   },
   {  
      "id":600,
      "question":"Why did the blonde keep a coat hanger in her back seat?",
      "answer":" In case she locks the keys in her car."
   },
   {  
      "id":601,
      "question":"Why did the blonde keep ice cubes in the freezer?",
      "answer":" To keep the refrigerator cold."
   },
   {  
      "id":602,
      "question":"Why did the blonde nurse take a red magic marker to work?",
      "answer":" In case she had to draw some blood."
   },
   {  
      "id":603,
      "question":"Why did the blonde plug her power strip back into itself?",
      "answer":" To save electricity."
   },
   {  
      "id":604,
      "question":"Why did the blonde put lipstick on her forehead?",
      "answer":" Because she was trying to make up her mind."
   },
   {  
      "id":605,
      "question":"Why did the blonde return a scarf to the store?",
      "answer":" Because it was too tight."
   },
   {  
      "id":606,
      "question":"Why did the blonde sell her car?",
      "answer":" She needed gas money."
   },
   {  
      "id":607,
      "question":"Why did the blonde stare at the frozen orange juice?",
      "answer":" Because it said Concentrate."
   },
   {  
      "id":608,
      "question":"Why did the blonde take a ruler to bed?",
      "answer":" To see how long she slept."
   },
   {  
      "id":609,
      "question":"Why did the blonde tip toe past the medicine cabinet?",
      "answer":" She didn't want to wake the sleeping pills."
   },
   {  
      "id":610,
      "question":"Why did the blonde want to become a veterinarian?",
      "answer":" Because she loved children."
   },
   {  
      "id":611,
      "question":"Why did the boy bring a ladder to school?",
      "answer":" He wanted to see what high school was like."
   },
   {  
      "id":612,
      "question":"Why did the boy sit on his watch?",
      "answer":" He wanted to be on time."
   },
   {  
      "id":613,
      "question":"Why did the boy stand behind the horse?",
      "answer":" He thought he might get a kick out of it."
   },
   {  
      "id":614,
      "question":"Why did the burglar take a shower?",
      "answer":" He wanted to make a clean getaway."
   },
   {  
      "id":615,
      "question":"Why did the cat cross the road?",
      "answer":" To prove he wasn't chicken."
   },
   {  
      "id":616,
      "question":"Why did the cat put oil on the mouse?",
      "answer":" Because it squeaked."
   },
   {  
      "id":617,
      "question":"Why did the cat run from the tree?",
      "answer":" Because it was afraid of the bark!"
   },
   {  
      "id":618,
      "question":"Why did the cat sleep with a fan on?",
      "answer":" He wanted to be a cool cat."
   },
   {  
      "id":619,
      "question":"Why did the chicken cross the playground?",
      "answer":" To get to the other slide."
   },
   {  
      "id":620,
      "question":"Why did the clock get sick?",
      "answer":" It was run down."
   },
   {  
      "id":621,
      "question":"Why did the computer go to the chiropractor?",
      "answer":" It had a slipped disc."
   },
   {  
      "id":622,
      "question":"Why did the fish blush?",
      "answer":" Because it saw the ocean's bottom."
   },
   {  
      "id":623,
      "question":"Why did the gardener plant his money?",
      "answer":" He wanted the soil to be rich."
   },
   {  
      "id":624,
      "question":"Why did the hen get in trouble?",
      "answer":" For using fowl language."
   },
   {  
      "id":625,
      "question":"Why did the house go to the doctor?",
      "answer":" It had window pane."
   },
   {  
      "id":626,
      "question":"Why did the judge dismiss the entire jury made up of cats?",
      "answer":" Because each of them was guilty of purrjury."
   },
   {  
      "id":627,
      "question":"Why did the king go to the dentist?",
      "answer":" To get his teeth crowned."
   },
   {  
      "id":628,
      "question":"Why did the lion spit out the clown?",
      "answer":" Because he tasted funny."
   },
   {  
      "id":629,
      "question":"Why did the litter of communist kittens become capitalists?",
      "answer":" Because they finally opened their eyes."
   },
   {  
      "id":630,
      "question":"Why did the man put a clock under his desk?",
      "answer":" He wanted to work overtime."
   },
   {  
      "id":631,
      "question":"Why did the man put his money in the freezer?",
      "answer":" Because he wanted cold hard cash."
   },
   {  
      "id":632,
      "question":"Why did the man run around his bed?",
      "answer":" Because he wanted to catch up on his sleep."
   },
   {  
      "id":633,
      "question":"Why did the moron climb the glass wall?",
      "answer":" To see what was on the other side."
   },
   {  
      "id":634,
      "question":"Why did the mother cat move her kittens?",
      "answer":" She didn't want to litter."
   },
   {  
      "id":635,
      "question":"Why did the mother cat put stamps on her kittens?",
      "answer":" Because she wanted to mail a litter."
   },
   {  
      "id":636,
      "question":"Why did the pony cough?",
      "answer":" He was a little hoarse."
   },
   {  
      "id":637,
      "question":"Why did the teacher wear sunglasses?",
      "answer":" Because she had bright students."
   },
   {  
      "id":638,
      "question":"Why did the turkey cross the road?",
      "answer":" It was the chicken's day off."
   },
   {  
      "id":639,
      "question":"Why did the turtle cross the road?",
      "answer":" To get to the Shell station."
   },
   {  
      "id":640,
      "question":"Why did the two knives go to the dance together?",
      "answer":" Because they both looked sharp."
   },
   {  
      "id":641,
      "question":"Why did the woman take a loaf of bread to bed with her?",
      "answer":" To feed her nightmare."
   },
   {  
      "id":642,
      "question":"Why did the woman wear a helmet at the dinner table?",
      "answer":" She was on a crash diet."
   },
   {  
      "id":643,
      "question":"Why didn't the piglets listen to the teacher pig?",
      "answer":" Because he was an old boar."
   },
   {  
      "id":644,
      "question":"Why didn't the hot dog star in the movies?",
      "answer":" The rolls weren't good enough."
   },
   {  
      "id":645,
      "question":"Why do birds fly south in the winter?",
      "answer":" Because it's too far to walk."
   },
   {  
      "id":646,
      "question":"Why do blondes drive BMW's?",
      "answer":" Because they can spell it."
   },
   {  
      "id":647,
      "question":"Why do blondes hate M&Ms?",
      "answer":" They're too hard to peel."
   },
   {  
      "id":648,
      "question":"Why do blondes have TGIF written on their shoes?",
      "answer":" To remind themselves that toes go in first."
   },
   {  
      "id":649,
      "question":"Why do blondes love lightning?",
      "answer":" They think somebody is taking their photo."
   },
   {  
      "id":650,
      "question":"Why do blondes wear earmuffs?",
      "answer":" To avoid the draft."
   },
   {  
      "id":651,
      "question":"Why do blondes wear shoulder pads?",
      "answer":" To keep from bruising their ears."
   },
   {  
      "id":652,
      "question":"Why do blondes wear their hair up?",
      "answer":" To catch as much as they can that goes over their heads."
   },
   {  
      "id":653,
      "question":"Why do cats like to hear other cats make noise?",
      "answer":" It's mewsic to their ears!"
   },
   {  
      "id":654,
      "question":"Why do elephants have trunks?",
      "answer":" Because they would look silly with glove compartments."
   },
   {  
      "id":655,
      "question":"Why do golfers wear 2 pairs of pants?",
      "answer":" In case they get a hole in one."
   },
   {  
      "id":656,
      "question":"Why do gorillas have big nostrils?",
      "answer":" Because they have big fingers."
   },
   {  
      "id":657,
      "question":"Why do hens lay eggs?",
      "answer":" If they drop them, they would break."
   },
   {  
      "id":658,
      "question":"Why do Hummingbirds hum?",
      "answer":" They've never learned the words."
   },
   {  
      "id":659,
      "question":"Why do people go to bed?",
      "answer":" Because the bed won't come to them."
   },
   {  
      "id":660,
      "question":"Why do traffic lights rarely go swimming?",
      "answer":" They take much too long to change."
   },
   {  
      "id":661,
      "question":"Why do two skunks argue?",
      "answer":" Because they like to kick up a stink."
   },
   {  
      "id":662,
      "question":"Why do you always find the cat in the last place you look?",
      "answer":" Because you stop looking after you find it."
   },
   {  
      "id":663,
      "question":"Why does a dog scratch himself?",
      "answer":" He is the only one who knows where it itches."
   },
   {  
      "id":664,
      "question":"Why does it take longer to build a blonde snowman as opposed to a regular one?",
      "answer":" You have to hollow out the head."
   },
   {  
      "id":665,
      "question":"Why don't blondes like audio books?",
      "answer":" There are no pictures."
   },
   {  
      "id":666,
      "question":"Why don't cats shave?",
      "answer":" Because they prefer whiskers."
   },
   {  
      "id":667,
      "question":"Why don't blondes eat pickles?",
      "answer":" Because they can't get their head in the jar."
   },
   {  
      "id":668,
      "question":"Why don't blondes have elevator jobs?",
      "answer":" Because they can't remember the route."
   },
   {  
      "id":669,
      "question":"Why don't cats play poker in the jungle?",
      "answer":" Too many cheetahs."
   },
   {  
      "id":670,
      "question":"Why is a dog's nose in the middle of its face?",
      "answer":" Because it's the scenter."
   },
   {  
      "id":671,
      "question":"Why is Alabama the smartest state in the USA?",
      "answer":" Because it has 4 A's and 1 B."
   },
   {  
      "id":672,
      "question":"Why is baseball like a cake?",
      "answer":" They both need batters."
   },
   {  
      "id":673,
      "question":"Why is Dracula so unpopular?",
      "answer":" He's a pain in the neck."
   },
   {  
      "id":674,
      "question":"Why is it so hard for a leopard to hide?",
      "answer":" Because he's always spotted."
   },
   {  
      "id":675,
      "question":"Why is it so hot in a stadium after a football game?",
      "answer":" Because all the fans have left."
   },
   {  
      "id":676,
      "question":"Why is money called dough?",
      "answer":" Because we call knead it."
   },
   {  
      "id":677,
      "question":"Why is the bride always out of luck on her wedding day?",
      "answer":" Because she never marries the best man."
   },
   {  
      "id":678,
      "question":"Why is the cat so grouchy?",
      "answer":" Because he's in a bad mewd."
   },
   {  
      "id":679,
      "question":"Why is the snail the strongest animal?",
      "answer":" Because he carries a house on his back."
   },
   {  
      "id":680,
      "question":"Why shouldn't blondes have coffee breaks?",
      "answer":" It takes too long to re-train them."
   },
   {  
      "id":681,
      "question":"Why was 6 afraid of 7?",
      "answer":" Because 7-8-9."
   },
   {  
      "id":682,
      "question":"Why was Santa's little helper depressed?",
      "answer":" Because he had low elf-esteem."
   },
   {  
      "id":683,
      "question":"Why was the banker bored?",
      "answer":" Because he lost interest in everything."
   },
   {  
      "id":684,
      "question":"Why was the blonde confused after giving birth to twins?",
      "answer":" She couldn't figure out who the other mother was."
   },
   {  
      "id":685,
      "question":"Why was the blonde so excited when she finished a jigsaw puzzle in 6 months?",
      "answer":" Because the box said, 2-4 years."
   },
   {  
      "id":686,
      "question":"Why was the cookie crying?",
      "answer":" Because it felt so crummy."
   },
   {  
      "id":687,
      "question":"Why was the lady's hair angry?",
      "answer":" Because she was always teasing it."
   },
   {  
      "id":688,
      "question":"Why was the little strawberry crying?",
      "answer":" Because his parents were in a jam."
   },
   {  
      "id":689,
      "question":"Why was Tigger looking in the toilet?",
      "answer":" He was trying to find Pooh."
   },
   {  
      "id":690,
      "question":"Why won't a witch wear a flat cap?",
      "answer":" Because there's no point in it."
   },
   {  
      "id":691,
      "question":"Why won't a bicycle stand up when it's not moving?",
      "answer":" It's too tired."
   },
   {  
      "id":692,
      "question":"Why won't they hire blondes as pharmacists?",
      "answer":" They keep breaking the prescription bottles in the typewriter."
   },
   {  
      "id":693,
      "question":"Why would Snow White be a good judge?",
      "answer":" Because she was the fairest in the land."
   }
]